
export const quizQuestions_1 = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the || operator in JavaScript?',
      choices: [
        'To perform logical AND operation',
        'To perform logical OR operation',
        'To check if a variable is null',
        'To concatenate two strings',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'To perform logical OR operation',
    },
    {
      question: 'How does the && operator behave in JavaScript?',
      choices: [
        'It returns true if either operand is true',
        'It returns true if both operands are true',
        'It returns false if either operand is false',
        'It returns false if both operands are false',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'It returns true if both operands are true',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which operator is used for nullish coalescing in JavaScript?',
      choices: [
        '|| operator',
        '&& operator',
        '?? operator',
        '?: operator',
      ],
      correctAnswer: '?? operator',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the result of the expression: true || false?',
      choices: [
        'true',
        'false',
        'null',
        'undefined',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'true',
    },
    {
      question: 'In short-circuit evaluation, when using the || operator, what is returned if the first operand is truthy?',
      choices: [
        'The first operand',
        'The second operand',
        'true',
        'false',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'The first operand',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the result of the expression: false && true?',
      choices: [
        'true',
        'false',
        'null',
        'undefined',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'false',
    },
    {
      question: 'In short-circuit evaluation, when using the && operator, what is returned if the first operand is falsy?',
      choices: [
        'The first operand',
        'The second operand',
        'true',
        'false',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'The first operand',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the result of the expression: null ?? "default"',
      choices: [
        'null',
        '"default"',
        'undefined',
        'true',
      ],
      correctAnswer: '"default"',
    },
    {
      question: 'In the context of short-circuiting, what is the purpose of using the ?? operator?',
      choices: [
        'To perform logical AND operation',
        'To provide a default value when the left operand is null or undefined',
        'To perform logical OR operation',
        'To check if a variable is null',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'To provide a default value when the left operand is null or undefined',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the result of the expression: "value" ?? "default"',
      choices: [
        '"value"',
        '"default"',
        'null',
        'undefined',
      ],
      correctAnswer: '"value"',
    },
  ],
}